[
 {
   "No": 1,
   "Quiz question": "What is the capital of Australia?",
   "Answer": "Canberra"
 },
 {
   "No": 2,
   "Quiz question": "What is the name of an evergreen tree or bush that grows in Australia?",
   "Answer": "Eucalyptus"
 },
 {
   "No": 3,
   "Quiz question": "Name a herbivorous marsupial living in Australia.",
   "Answer": "Koala"
 },
 {
   "No": 4,
   "Quiz question": "What is the largest city in Australia?",
   "Answer": "Sydney"
 },
 {
   "No": 5,
   "Quiz question": "What is the highest mountain on the continent?",
   "Answer": "Kosciuzko"
 },
 {
   "No": 6,
   "Quiz question": "What is Australia’s form of government?",
   "Answer": "Monarchy"
 },
 {
   "No": 7,
   "Quiz question": "Australia used to be a dominion of which country?",
   "Answer": "Great Britain"
 },
 {
   "No": 8,
   "Quiz question": "What is Australia’s rank by surface area in the world?",
   "Answer": "Sixth"
 },
 {
   "No": 9,
   "Quiz question": "What is the largest river in Australia?",
   "Answer": "River Murray"
 },
 {
   "No": 10,
   "Quiz question": "What is the population of Australia?",
   "Answer": "23 million"
 },
 {
   "No": 11,
   "Quiz question": "Is it true that Australia is a continent with the largest number of venomous things?",
   "Answer": "Yes, it is true."
 },
 {
   "No": 12,
   "Quiz question": "What is a distinct feature of Lake Eyre which is located in Australia?",
   "Answer": "It is the driest lake in the world"
 },
 {
   "No": 13,
   "Quiz question": "What is a feature of Australian currency?",
   "Answer": "The banknotes are made of plastic"
 },
 {
   "No": 14,
   "Quiz question": "Name the island located south of Australia.",
   "Answer": "Tasmania"
 },
 {
   "No": 15,
   "Quiz question": "What is the most venomous animal living in Australia?",
   "Answer": "Octopus"
 },
 {
   "No": 16,
   "Quiz question": "What climate zone is the majority of Australia in?",
   "Answer": "Tropical"
 },
 {
   "No": 17,
   "Quiz question": "Australia has the largest reserves of what metal?",
   "Answer": "Zirconium"
 },
 {
   "No": 18,
   "Quiz question": "Name a large sand-and-salt desert in Australia.",
   "Answer": "Victoria Desert"
 },
 {
   "No": 19,
   "Quiz question": "What is Australia’s lowest point?",
   "Answer": "The bottom of Lake Eyre: - 16 meters"
 },
 {
   "No": 20,
   "Quiz question": "What Australian animals are depicted on the country’s coins?",
   "Answer": "Lyre-bird and echidna"
 },
 {
   "No": 21,
   "Quiz question": "Name the gulf in the northern part of the continent.",
   "Answer": "Gulf of Carpentaria"
 },
 {
   "No": 22,
   "Quiz question": "Name the strait in the Pacific Ocean that separates Australia from New Guinea.",
   "Answer": "Torres Strait"
 },
 {
   "No": 23,
   "Quiz question": "Official language in Australia?",
   "Answer": "English"
 },
 {
   "No": 24,
   "Quiz question": "Who is the formal head of state in Australia?",
   "Answer": "The Queen"
 },
 {
   "No": 25,
   "Quiz question": "What is the most famous building in Sydney?",
   "Answer": "Opera"
 }
]
